<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Nexomon (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.Nexomon</packageId>
  <author>RavenousEye</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/Nexomon</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of RavenousEyes mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2241246944

[img]https://i.imgur.com/CN9Rs5X.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/Nexomon][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/vlKk9IU.png[/img]
This mod adds in animals called Nexomon from the Nexomon games. A monster catching genre like pokemon.
Currently has 11 Nexomon, more are in active development. Armor for each Nexomon are also in development.

Nexomon come with custom leather/wool types. (And soon custom sounds)

This mod also adds 2 new bills at the Art bench:
-Make Nexomon sculpture
-Make legendary Nexomon sculpture

This mod adds 1 new quest: Crashed nexomon ship. (crashed ship containing loot &amp;amp; injured nexomon to heal &amp;amp; recruit. (prepare first, it will be heavy guarded)

[img]https://i.imgur.com/B0AH3Hb.png[/img]
V1.7:
Added custom animal sounds (Thanks to Stormtail!)
Added More Vanilla Biomes patch.

V1.6:
Fixed few typo's in spawn rates &amp;amp; descriptions.
Small tweaks in some animal stats.

V1.5: 
          *Fixed Giddy up patch (pawns mounted on very awkward positions) fuzztino and draclone are mountable but shouldn't be, working on a fix to disable it by default. For now you can disable them in giddy up mod menu.
          *Added support for Alpha Biomes (Nexomon can now spawn)
          *Adjusted spawn rates some more.
          *Minor tweaks in some nexomon stats.
          *Fixed carry weight from nexomon in caravans.
          *Added new nexomon: Mystogen
          *Fixed nexomons spawning as pack that should spawn solo.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/CbnLN8A.png[/img]
-Uses Harmony (dependancy)
-Compatible with Animal Genetics
-Compatible with Giddy up (recommended)
-Compatible with Alpha Biomes
-Compatible with Cyber fauna

[img]https://i.imgur.com/iW3tCEL.png[/img]
Combat Extended (it might work but it's not tested)
A Dog Said (doesn't break, simply not supported)

[img]https://i.imgur.com/5us9tfi.png[/img]
Q: Can this mod be added to existing save file?
A: Yes

Q: is this mod Compatible with Combat Extended?
A: I don't use CE and will no make patches for it. It's not compatible with CE combat system, and gives some errors. 
     However it can be safely added without crashing. (except a few errors)

Q: How strong are the Nexomon compared to vanilla animals?
A: Nexomon are fairly tough, don't fight them unless you have a decent amount of firepower.

Q: Could you add x?
A: Feel free to share any ideas. If it sounds fun and do-able I would add it in.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/OI21Aw8.png[/img]
-More Nexomon (including Nexomon Extinction)
-Armor for all nexomon (current project)
-Custom sounds for all nexomon (current project)
-Ranged attacks / abilities &amp;amp; Custom behaviours (will have additional dependancy's so will be a different mod)

[img]https://i.imgur.com/xTEcyVc.png[/img]
Kasmex Forever for the art
Sielfyr for the coding
Ravvy for making all of the sculptures
Happy Taffy for assisting in art and some coding.
Stormtail for custom sounds of every nexomon.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/feGuNnY.png[/img]
https://rimworld-bestiary.fandom.com/wiki/Nexomon

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]</description>
</ModMetaData>